citymax.com 2010-08-28

# Website Builder Privacy Policy – Build Your Own Website with CityMax.com

CityMax is committed to protecting the privacy of each of its users. We want you to feel free to express yourself within your web pages (within legal limitations) and we are committed to allowing you to feel secure in your own private environment, putting you in control of what you share. 

## CityMax.com Privacy Policy 

CityMax values the privacy of visitors to its site. This Privacy Policy describes the type of information we collect from you, and what we do with that information. The privacy policy shall be accepted as part of the Terms of Service. 

### What personal information does CityMax collect?

CityMax collects your name and e-mail address, and phone number when you first register on the site. We also ask for additional, optional information through our registration form, including but not limited to your address, fax number and demographic information. 

CityMax uses a standard Internet technology called "cookies" to store and track visitor information/sessions. A cookie is a small text file that a server can automatically store on your computer and retrieve later. We instruct your browser to place a "cookie" into a file on your hard drive when you visit our site. Each time you return to the site, the cookie is re-sent to us so that we may track which of our services you use and what content you view (including advertisements). In addition, we collect the Internet Protocol address of each visitor to our site, which is a number that can be used to identify your internet service provider, among other things.

### How does CityMax use the information it collects? 

CityMax is committed to respecting your privacy. We may disclose information we have collected from you and/or content you have made available on our site in the following circumstances, and also may disclose such information and/or content to others when CityMax believes in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of CityMax or its visitors.

Upon request CityMax may disclose your contact information to customers of your website, government agencies, any trademark or copyright owner requiring to contact you in regards to transactions or content on your site. 

Information submitted by you at the time of registration (including but not limited to your name and e-mail address) may be used but not limited to marketing and promotional purposes by CityMax. 

This information may also be shared with other companies who offer a service to CityMax or co-branded or rebranded versions of our site, who offer services in conjunction with CityMax, or who are business partners of CityMax. CityMax will not otherwise identify you personally to other companies, or to any advertisers. CityMax provides demographic information in aggregate form to advertisers on our site, without identifying any user personally. 

CityMax may disclose your website URL for tracking purposes to other sites that either have referred you to CityMax or for internal CityMax promotions. 

We may use information provided by you when you participate in contests or surveys on our site to send information about CityMax to you, or to give information to advertisers in aggregate form. 

We use cookies to determine whether you are logged on to our site, to maintain your session, and to automatically log you out if your computer remains idle for a specified amount of time when using our service. We also use cookies to measure the traffic on our site, track which of our services you use, which content you view (including advertisements) and how long you view it. We collect IP addresses for administrative purposes (such as to help diagnose problems with our server) and to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors. 

**You agree to allow us to contact you via mail, email and telephone for the purpose of activation, service or billing, even if you are on the Federal Do Not Call List. You agree not to report our email communications to you as SPAM to anyone to any governing body, ISP or service provider since you are able to opt in or opt out of any mailings you request and agree to receive.**

### How to get more information? 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact us through either the email support feature in your website (log in at "CityMax", go to "help", "ask at question to support", "other") or through the email help feature on the CityMax home page (go to the help link, "ask a question"). Or by mail to 313 - 1 Alexander Street, Vancouver, BC V6A 1B2 Canada. 

### General

If any provision of this Agreement is held to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be struck and the remaining provisions shall be enforced. CityMax's failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Agreement shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision. You shall not assign this Agreement or any rights or obligations hereunder, by operation of law or otherwise, without prior written approval of CityMax, and any such attempted assignment shall be void.

CityMax shall have the right to freely assign this Agreement, and its rights and obligations hereunder, to any third party without requiring the consent or notice of you. Subject to the foregoing, this Agreement shall be binding upon and inure to the benefits of the parties hereto, their successors and permitted assigns. This Agreement sets forth the entire understanding and agreement between CityMax and you with respect to the subject matter hereof. Each party is an independent contractor and not an agent or representative of any other party. No party shall have any right or authority to create any obligation or make any representation or warranty in the name or on behalf of any other party. This Agreement shall not be interpreted or construed to create an association, joint venture or partnership between the parties or to impose any partnership obligation or liability upon any party. The parties acknowledge and agree that this Agreement may be entered into electronically, and without the necessity of written signatures.
